(Raj:)Just straight to,
"Where's the other white guy?"
(Leonard:)I'm sorry.
(Leonard:)So, listen, I heard something about him.
Can you keep it between us?
(Raj:)Ooh, gossip. When I first got here...
...I thought Americans really gossiped
around the water cooler.
I hung out there for a month,
but the only gossip I heard...
(Raj:)...was about some creepy guy
hanging out by the water cooler.
(Leonard:)Bernadette wants to get a prenup.
(Raj:)Oh, that's a shame.
He's gonna be devastated.
(Leonard:)I never know what to do
in these situations.
- Should I give him a heads up?
- Hmm.
I'm gonna give you the advice
I yell at the TV...
(Raj:)...when the Bachelor
is handing out roses.
(Raj:)Follow your heart.
(Howard:)Check it out.
(Howard:)Look at the size of that
Rice Krispie Treat. Same price, ha, ha.
Ahem, hey, Howard,
I need to tell you something.
(Howard:)I know, it's not on my wedding diet.
I don't care.
No. Listen, I heard that Bernadette's thinking
about asking you for a prenup.